https://www.royallifesaving.com.au/privacy

PLEASE NOTE
There may be changes to course offerings in your local area as a ...
Stay up-to-date and keep pace with the aquatic industry
Royal Life Saving believes everyone can be a lifesaver. Whether as a responsible member of the community or for a lifesaving career, the skills you learn are skills for life.
Find a Course
Booking Details
Frequently Asked QuestionsGroup BookingsOnline Shop Training Enquiries
Families
At Home
Kids Activities
Toddler Drowning Prevention
Keep Watch Actions
Keep Watch Lifestages
Keep Watch @ Bath Time
Keep Watch @ The Farm
First Aid
Resuscitation (CPR)
At the Local Pool
Swim and Survive
Lifesaving Programs
Bronze Medallion
Grey Medallion
Pool Lifesaving
Drowning Prevention
Keep Watch at Public Pools
Alcohol and Water Safety
We want you to be safe when you’re at home, at the local pool, or out & about. Our courses, programs & resources are designed to keep your family safe, no matter where you are
Read more
Schools
In the Classroom
Home Learning COVID-19
Water Smart
Water Smart Education Toolkit
Water Smart Award
E-Lifesaving
First Aid
Resuscitation (CPR)
At the Pool
Swim and Survive
Lifesaving Programs
Bronze Medallion
Pool Lifesaving
Facility Standards
5 Star Aquatic Facilities
Out and About
Drowning and Epilepsy
Lifesaving can take you from the classroom to the pool to anywhere there is water. Royal Life Saving offers custom programs and resources designed specifically for schools.
Read More
Aquatic
Pool Lifeguards
Lifeguarding Careers
Becoming a Lifeguard
International Lifeguards
Pool Operations
Professional Development
State of the Industry
Lifeguards, swim teachers and facility managers all have important jobs ensuring the safety of others. Learn more about careers, professional development and resources here
Read More
About
Who we are
Background
Governance
Annual Reports
Member Organisations
Australian Capital Territory
Western Australia
Royal Life Saving is active across Australia serving the community for the past 125yrs. Royal Life Saving works to prevent drowning and facilitate healthy active lifestyles.
Read More
Facts & Figures
Key Facts
Activities and Equipment
Child Safe Play Areas
Children's Pool Party Safety
Mermaid Tails and Monofins
Lifejackets
Summer Drowning Toll
Whatever your information requirements are you will find countless tips, facts, checklists and general research information regarding water safety here
Read More
Programs
Keep Watch
Keep Watch Actions
Supervise
Restrict
Teach
Respond
ACT Swim 4 Life Program
CALD/NESB (Non english speaking)
Disabilities
International
International Projects (Includes Partners)
Global Drowning Fund
Our programs have been developed so all Australian's can have the awareness, skills and knowledge to safely participate in a range of aquatic activities.
Read More
Pool Lifesaving
No matter what your age is or how well you swim, there’s plenty of opportunities for everyone to enjoy and learn with Pool Lifesaving.
Read More
Donate
Swim and Survive Fund
Global Drowning Fund
Fundraise for us
You can make a real difference by helping us to implement and deliver water safety education programs across Australia.
Read More
Privacy
Home
Privacy
Privacy
The Royal Life Saving Society – Website is operated in compliance with the Privacy Amendment (Enhancing Privacy Protection) Act 2012 (Commonwealth). Any information you submit through the Website will be dealt with in accordance with the 13 National Privacy Principles:Open and transparent management of personal information Anonymity and pseudonymityCollection of solicited personal informationDealing with unsolicited personal informationNotification of the collection of personal informationUse or disclosure of personal informationDirect marketingCross-border disclosure of personal informationAdoption, use or disclosure of government related identifiersQuality of personal informationSecurity of personal informationAccess to personal informationCorrection of personal informationClick here for more information about the 13 privacy principles.
If you visit the Site and register, enter competitions or ask for further information, our system will record the details you submit and will only use the information you have provided for the purposes for which the information was provided to us. We will take steps to safeguard our systems to protect your information from misuse and loss. If at any stage you cancel your registration, or your application for any further information, or log out prior to submitting your entry or application, the information you have entered up to that point will be automatically deleted. If you have any complaints about the way in which we have dealt with your personal information please contact us.Email: marketing@rlssa.org.au
National Manager Events and Marketing
Royal Life Saving Society – Australia PO Box 558 Broadway NSW 2007 Telephone: (02) 8217 3123
